Guide to the Film Arts Foundation Collection M1897
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Film Arts Foundation collection
1984-2000
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Film Arts Foundation (San Francisco, Calif.)
M1897
5 Linear Feet (422 audiocassettes in 12 boxes)
693 computer file(s) (mp3) (422 cassettes from 216 events)
Audio recordings of lectures and workshops about independent film production sponsored by the Film Arts Foundation, 1984-2000.
Biographical / Historical
The Film Arts Foundation was a non-profit organization founded by independent filmmakers in San Francisco, California in 1976, providing services such as professional training, equipment, information, consultations and exhibition opportunities to support artists across the Bay Area. FAF offered a film festival, exhibitions, workshops, grants, fiscal sponsorship programs, and an equipment rental facility. They also published the magazine Release Print. In 2008, they were absorbed by the San Francisco Film Society.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from Media-Microtext, Accession 2012-096.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Content has been transferred and is available digitally. Non-Stanford-affiliated patrons may access files in Green Library.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of over 400 audiocassettes recording lectures and workshops hosted by FAF in the 1990s, including many sessions from the International Film Financing Conference (IFFCON). Participants include Les Blank, Errol Morris, Caveh Zahedi, Millard Kaufman, Denise Bostrom, Hiro Narita, Debra Chasnoff, Brodsky & Treadway, and Kenn Rabin. These cassettes have been digitized and cataloged individually. More information can be found here: http://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/9704519 and here: http://searchworks.stanford.edu/catalog?f%5Bcollection%5D%5B%5D=9704519 Audio files are available from Searchworks for Stanford-affiliated patrons. Files may also be accessed from Stanford's Green Library reading room.
Related Materials
UC Berkeley's Bancroft Library holds the Film Arts Foundation records.
Independent films; Motion picture industry.; Motion pictures -- Production and direction; Film Arts Foundation (San Francisco, Calif.)
- Deep in the Heart of Taxes (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-9-1995 (Box 1)
- Script Continuity Denise Bostrum (tapes 1-3 of 4), 3-19-1994 (Box 1)
- Feature Fix-Financial Management (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-26-1992 (Box 1)
- Feature Fix-Steal American-Case Study (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-12-1992 (Box 1)
- Professionals in Film: Hiro Narita (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 2-14-1989 (Box 1)
- Does Radical Content Require Radical Form (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 1)
- Scripting a Business Plan (tapes 1 and 2 of 2), 2-18-1999 (Box 1)
- Sundance Prep Talk (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 1-13-1999 (Box 1)
- IFFCON '95 Understanding of Tools of Selling (tapes 4 & 5 of 14) (Box 1)
- Low to no Budget Films Apparatus Productions (tapes 1-4 of 4), 6-8-1991 (Box 2)
- An Evening with Film Composer Todd Boekelheide (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-20-1991 (Box 2)
- Meet the Funders: Minority Consortia (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-25-1992 (Box 2)
- An Evening with Flower Films: Les Blank, Maureen Gosling, Chris Simon (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-7-1992 (Box 2)
- An Evening with David Goldie (tapes 1 -3 of 3), 6-10-1993 (Box 2)
- Meet the Funder: CCH Stan Yogi (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-14-1993 (Box 2)
- An Evening with Caveh Zahedi (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 5-4-1994 (Box 2)
- Doc. Revealed: Develop. Your Project Cole, Saraf, Odom, Wood (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-8-1994 (Box 2)
- Breaking Into Post - Prod. Lisa Storer, 6-28-1994 (Box 2)
- Reflexions: The Documentary in Crisis Towards Reflexive Documentary Form (tapes 2-4 of 4), 05-1985 (Box 2)
- Super-8 in the video age Bob Brodsky/Toni Treadway (tapes 1-3 of 3), 6-11-1985 (Box 2)
- Visual Aesthetics Bob Brodsky/Tony Treadway (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-13-1985 (Box 2)
- Documentary Producer's Workshop: Directing & Editing Docs (tapes 1 & 2 of 3), 5-2-1991 (Box 2)
- Documentary Producer's Workshop: Directing & Editing Docs (tapes 1-3 of 3), 5-9-1991 (Box 2)
- Documentary Producer's Workshop: The Historical Doc & Cinema Verite (tapes 2 & 3 of 3), 5-16-1991 (Box 2)
- Low to no Budget Filmmaking with Apparatus Productions (tapes 3 & 4 of 4), 6-8-1991 (Box 2)
- Anatomy of a Feature #2 Money to make that feature (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-10-1994 (Box 3)
- Anatomy of a Feature #4 Perilous Pleasures of Post - Production (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-17-1994 (Box 3)
- Anatomy of a Feature #5 Dissecting Suture (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-19-1994 (Box 3)
- Anatomy of a Feature #6 Indie Film Distribution (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-24-1994 (Box 3)
- Anatomy of a Feature #7 First-Time Filmmakers Tell All! (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-26-1994 (Box 3)
- Making the news B.L.O. (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-18-1995 (Box 3)
- An Evening with the Robeson Fund (tape 1 of 1), 11-12-1996 (Box 3)
- Pedal to the medal: How to make a music video (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-13-1996 (Box 3)
- Fame, Fortune, Fabulous Prizes w/ Panavision, Robeson, Aperture (tape 1 of 1), 11-7-1996 (Box 3)
- Entering Festivals (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-21-1996 (Box 3)
- Forbidden Planets: Outer Limits of Film Getting It made (tape 2 of 2), 10-14-1992 (Box 3)
- Forbidden Planets: Outer Limits of Film Getting It out (tape 1 of 2), 10-21-1992 (Box 3)
- Forbidden Planets: Outer Limits of Film Getting It out (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-21-1992 (Box 3)
- Make-Up for Film & Video, 11-15-1992 (Box 3)
- Artists Working with Multimedia: Hershman, Campbell, LeGrady, et al (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-21-1993 (Box 3)
- Video: Preparing for an On-line Eric Ladenburg (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-12-1993 (Box 3)
- Panavision's New Filmmaker Program Gregory Ruzzin (tape 1 of 1), 11-29-1993 (Box 3)
- Panavision's New Filmmaker Program Gregory Ruzzin (tape 1 of 1), 11-29-1993 (Box 3)
- Anatomy of Feature #1 World According to John Pierson (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-5-1994 (Box 3)
- An Evening with ILM (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-14-1997 (Box 3)
- An Evening with Richard C. Zimmerman (tape 1 of 1), 10-21-1997 (Box 3)
- An Evening with Richard C. Zimmerman (tape 1 of 1), 10-21-1997 (Box 3)
- Killer Animators: J. Cantor (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-7-1997 (Box 3)
- Super 8 extravaganza Bob Brodsky & Toni Treadway (tapes 1-3 of 4), 12-12-1992 (Box 4)
- Post-IFP Market Round up Peter Moore (tape 1 of 1), 12-2-1993 (Box 4)
- Distribution: Getting the Work out there Hawk/Moore (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 12-7-1993 (Box 4)
- Distribution: Strand Releasing Jon Gerrans and Marcus Hu (tape 2 of 2), 12-9-1993 (Box 4)
- Navigating Educational Media Markets: Distribution Tips (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 12-13-1994 (Box 4)
- Post-Production Primer for Beginners (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-18-1997 (Box 4)
- An Evening with John Pierson (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 12-4-1997 (Box 4)
- Desktop Digital: Editing for Film w/ Filmlogic (tapes 1-3 of 3), 12-12-1998 (Box 4)
- Proposal Writing Crash Course with Julie Mackman (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 12-15-1998 (Box 4)
- Inside the Fuel Film Tour (tape 1 of 1), 10-25-1997 (Box 4)
- Post-production Primer For Beginners (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-18-1997 (Box 4)
- Equipment Rental House Round-up (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-20-1997 (Box 4)
- Going Digital: Breakthrough Ultra-Low Budget Filmmaking with Peter Broderick (tapes 1-3 of 3), 10-15-1998 (Box 4)
- An Evening with the Creative Workfund (tape 1 of 1), 11-11-1998 (Box 4)
- Meet the Funder: An En Evening with the Paul Robeson Fund (tape 1 of 1), 11-18-1998 (Box 4)
- Proposal Writing: A Crash Course (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-18-1999 (Box 4)
- The Hollywood Script Reader (tapes 1-3 of 3), 11-13-1999 (Box 4)
- An Evening with ILM (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-14-1997 (Box 4)
- Distribution: Strand Releasing Jon Gerrans and Marcus Hu (tape 1 of 2), 12-09-1993 (Box 4)
- Turn on Digital TV (tape 2 of 2), 3-13-1999 (Box 5)
- The Screenwriter's Workshop SYD Field (tapes 1-5 of 5), 2-16/17-1985 (Box 5)
- Screenwriting Panel Discussion Film Arts Festival 1990 Hillman, Corr, Kelly, Larner, Rathod (Box 5)
- The Making of "El Norte" Nava/Thomas (tape 1 of 1), 2-26-1984 (Box 5)
- IFFCON '94 Opening Reception (tapes 1-7 of 7), 1-13-94 - 1-16-1994 (Box 5)
- Berlin Festival Prep-Talk Nancy Fishman (tape 1 of 1), 1-31-1994 (Box 5)
- IFFCON '95 Introductions (Box 5)
- IFFCON '95 Rallying US Dollars Rallying US Dollar (tape 2 of 14) (Box 5)
- IFFCON '95 Navigating European Film Funds (tape 3 of 14) (Box 5)
- Camera, Hiro Narita (tapes 1 & 3 of 4), 3/24/1984 (Box 5)
- The Screenwriter's Workshop SYD Field, 2-16-1985 through 2-17-1985 (Box 5)
- Feature Fix-Financing Features (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-19-1992 (Box 5)
- How to throw a fundraising party (tape 2 of 2), 3-24-1993 (Box 5)
- Script Continuity Denise Bostrum (tape 4 of 4), 3-19-1994 (Box 5)
- Meet the Filmmakers: Alan Jacobs Director of Nina Takes a Lover (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-11-1995 (Box 5)
- Scripting a Business Plan for Film (tapes 1-4 of 4), 3-21-1995 through 3-22-1995 (Box 5)
- Post Production Primer for Beginners (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-13-1997 (Box 5)
- Dramatic Roundtable: Discussion with Directors from NAATA Festival (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-8-1998 (Box 5)
- Turn on Digital TV (tape 1 of 2), 3-13-1999 (Box 5)
- Turning into Cable (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-24-1998 (Box 6)
- An Evening with P.O.V. (tape 1 of 1), 6-9-1999 (Box 6)
- Art Direction on a Budget (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-26-1999 (Box 6)
- Tall Tales from Short Stack: Projection Predicament (tape 2 of 2), 6-24-1996 (Box 6)
- An Evening with Chantal Akerman (tape 1 of 1), 5-10-1997 (Box 6)
- An Evening with NEH Holly Tank (tape 2 of 2), 5-18-1994 (Box 6)
- Midnight Ramble: the Race Movie Pamela Thomas (tape 1 of 1), 5-22-1994 (Box 6)
- Film/Video Careers: Production Mgmt. Karen Aschlenbach (tape 2 of 2), 6-3-1987 (Box 6)
- A Day with Vilmos Zsigmond Master Cinematographer (tapes 1 -4 of 4), 7-18-1987 (Box 6)
- The Art of Music for Film Gary Remal, Composer (tape 1 of 1), 8-18-1985 (Box 6)
- Audio Formats for Location Sound Phil Perkins (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 8-28-1993 (Box 6)
- Hand Processing for Black & White Ross Lipman (tape 1 of 2), 9-23-1993 (Box 6)
- Breaking into Post- Prod. Lisa Storer (tape 2 of 2), 6-28-1994 (Box 6)
- Tall Tales/Short Stack: Alternative Distribution For Short Films (tapes 2 of 2), 6-03-1996 (Box 6)
- Tall Tales from the Short Stack: Cavalcade of Shorts (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-10-1996 (Box 6)
- Tall Tales from the Short Stack: Shelf Life for Shorts (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-17-1996 (Box 6)
- Envisioning the Digital Future (tapes 1-5 and 7-9 of 9), 6-22-1996 through 6/23/1996 (Box 6)
- An Evening with Rosa von Praunheim (tape 1 of 1), 7-15-1996 (Box 6)
- Music Video Production (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 6-17-1997 (Box 6)
- Focus on Do. An Eve. w/ Debra Chasnoff (tape 2 of 2), 2-26-1998 (Box 7)
- IFFCON 1996 Reel 5 (tape 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- IFFCON 1996 Reel 6, 1-14-1996 (Box 7)
- Navigating European Film Funds IFFCON 96 (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- The Pitch IFFCON '96 (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- IFFCON '96 Saturday (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- Rallying US Dollars IFFCON 96 (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- International Television (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- International Distribution (tapes 1 & 2 of 2) (Box 7)
- Deep in the Heart of Texas (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 2-15-1996 (Box 7)
- Focus on Doc. An Evening with Debra Chasnoff (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 2-26-1998 (Box 7)
- An Evening with AFI (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 1-15-1998 (Box 7)
- Copy, Festival, Exposure, Meals: Keeping Actors Happy (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 1-26-1998 (Box 7)
- Focus on Doc. An Evening with Allie Light & Irving Saraf (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 2-12-1998 (Box 7)
- The DVC Revolution (tapes 1-4 of 4), 2-27-1997 (Box 7)
- Sundance Film Festival: A Prep Talk (tape 1 of 1), 1-8-1998 (Box 7)
- Production Management (tapes 3 & 4 of 4), 2-28-1996 and 2-27-1996 (Box 7)
- The DVC Revolution (tapes 1-4 of 4), 2-27-1997 (Box 7)
- The Creative Tool Curt McDowell (tape 1 of 1), 11-17-1984 (Box 8)
- Financing Features with Investors Lynn O'Donnell and Robert Heil (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-18-1988 (Box 8)
- Professionals in the Film: Jon Else (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-15-1990 (Box 8)
- ZDF (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-26-1991 (Box 8)
- ZDF Peter Naderman (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-27-1991 (Box 8)
- Corporate Fundraising (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 11-07-1991 (Box 8)
- Forbidden Planets: Outer Limits of Film Getting it Made, 10-14-1992 (Box 8)
- Pedal to the Metal (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 08-24-1999 (Box 8)
- An Evening with the Assistant Director (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 08-25-1999 (Box 8)
- Alternative Strategies I: Hand Processing (tape 1 of 1), 09-16-1999 (Box 8)
- Alternative Strategies II: Old and New Technologies (tape 1 of 1), 09-21-1999 (Box 8)
- Evening w/ Assistant Director's Training Program (tape 2 of 2), 9-23-1998 (Box 8)
- An Evening with Seventh Art Releasing (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-15-1999 (Box 8)
- Breaking into the Film Biz (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 08-23-1999 (Box 8)
- Bring on the Next Wave (Tape 1 of 1), 07-15-1997 (Box 8)
- Non-Profit (tape 2 of 2), 09-15-1992 (Box 8)
- IFP Market: A Prep Talk Peter Moore (tape 1 of 1), 09-09-1993 (Box 8)
- Forbidden Planets: Outer Limits of Film Aesthetics & Content (tape 1 of 2), 10-28-1992 (Box 8)
- Setting up your own Non-profit Richard Lee (tape 1 of 2), 09-15-1992 (Box 8)
- Getting Rights & Keeping Them Roberta Cairney & Peter Franck (tape 1 of 2), 10-25-1988 (Box 8)
- An Evening with Millard Kaufman (tape 1 of 1), 09-27-1999 (Box 8)
- Alternative Strategies III: Beyond the White Wall (Tape 1 of 1), 09-30-1999 (Box 8)
- Muncy/Sperling (tape 1 of 1) DUB, 10-18-1995 (Box 8)
- Errol Morris DUB, 09-22-1997 (Box 8)
- In the Eye of the Storm: The Art of Documentary Cinematography (tape 2 of 2), 09-25-1996 (Box 8)
- Meet the Funder: ITVS Jim Yee (tape 1 of 2), 07-06-1994 (Box 8)
- Focus on Screenwriting Ehren Kruger (tape 2 of 2), 08-18-1999 (Box 8)
- Reflexions: The Documentary in Crisis The Point of View (tape 1 of 4), 05-1985 (Box 9)
- Setting up your own Nonprofit (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-13-1998 (Box 9)
- TV Party! (tape 1 & 2 of 2), 04-21-1999 (Box 9)
- Forming a Limited Partnership (tape 2 of 2), 04-14-1998 (Box 9)
- Sound Affects: Sound Recording (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-15-1999 (Box 9)
- Sound Affects III: The Mix (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-22-1999 (Box 9)
- Fiscal Sponsorship, 04-18-2000 (Box 9)
- Fiscal Sponsorship Gail Silva, 04-18-2000 (Box 9)
- An Evening with NEH Holly Tank (tape 1 of 2), 05-18-1994 (Box 9)
- Screenwriting Guidance Straight from The Source (tape 2 of 2), 04-02-1998 (Box 9)
- Archival Footage w/ Kenn Rabin (tape 2 of 6), 03-22-1997 (Box 9)
- Forming a Limited Partnership (tape 1 of 2), 04-14-1998 (Box 9)
- Getting Ink: The Whys and Hows of Press Journalism (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-11-1996 (Box 9)
- Inside the Celluloid Closet (tape 1 of 2), 05-13-1996 (Box 9)
- Creating/Operating a Production Company Mitchell Block (tape 1 & 2 of 2), 05-19-1994 (Box 9)
- Insurance for Media Makers Charles Whelan (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-10-1995 (Box 9)
- Entering Festivals Gibbs panelists (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-12-1995 (Box 9)
- Mind your Bus.: Production Management Andrea Sperling & Karen Aschenbach (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-15-1993 (Box 9)
- Mind your Bus.: Financial Management Cynthia Gair (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-20-1993 (Box 9)
- Mind your own Business: Rights Hank Berry (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-22-1993 (Box 9)
- Mind your own Buisness: Publicity Karen Larsen & Mark Kitchell (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 04-27-1993 (Box 9)
- Camera, Hiro Narita (tape 2 of 4), 03-24-1984 (Box 9)
- Evening w/ Assistant Director's Training Program. (tape 1 of 2), 9-23-1998 (Box 10)
- Evening with New Independent Distributors (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-15-1998 (Box 10)
- Navigating the Educational Market (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-08-1998 (Box 10)
- The Video Vortex (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-01-1998 (Box 10)
- Focus on Sound Design: R. Beggs (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 9-16-1997 (Box 10)
- Focus on Editing: Debbie Hoffman (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 9-09-1997 (Box 10)
- Inside Turbulent Arts: Marc Smolowitz (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 8-13-1997 (Box 10)
- Anatomy of Fame Whore (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-22-1997 (Box 10)
- Self-Accounting for Filmmakers (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-27-1996 (Box 10)
- Start to Finish: Doing your own Publicity (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-23-1996 (Box 10)
- Cut to the Chase: Picture Editing (tape 1 & 2 of 2), 10-01-1996 (Box 10)
- In the Eye of the Storm: The Art of Narrative Cinematography (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 9-24-1996 (Box 10)
- The Making of Toy Story with Ralph Guggenheim (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 9-11-1996 (Box 10)
- An Evening with CCH: Ralph Lewin (tape 1 of 1), 9-10-1996 (Box 10)
- The Business of Independent Production Cherie Martin (tapes 1 - 5 of 5), 8-13-1994 through 8-14-1994 (Box 10)
- AFI Digital Independence Workshop (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 7-19-1994 (Box 10)
- An Evening with Eric Saks (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 10-06-1993 (Box 10)
- Hand Processing for Black & White Ross Lipman (tape 2 of 2), 09-23-1993 (Box 10)
- Negotiating Contracts Marc Greenberg (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-23-1993 (Box 11)
- How to throw a Fundraising Party (tape 1 of 21), 3-24-1993 (Box 11)
- Intro to Cinematography Phil Greene (tapes 1-3 of 3), 3-21-1984 (Box 11)
- Camera, Hiro Narita (tape 4 of 4), 3-24-1984 (Box 11)
- Archival Footage w/ Kenn Rabin (tape 1 & 3 of 6), 3-22-1997 (Box 11)
- Business Series - Home Video Distribution: Flower Films, Les Blank, S. Kell (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-16-1988 (Box 11)
- Filmmakers: Roundtable: SFAIFF (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-14-1999 (Box 11)
- Professionals in Film: Vivien Hillgrove Gilliam (tape 1 & 2 of 2), 3-14-1999 (Box 11)
- IFFCON Reel 5, 1-14-1996 (Box 11)
- IFFCON Reel 4 (tapes 1 & 2 of 7), 1-14-1996 (Box 11)
- Production Management, 2-27-1996 (Box 11)
- Forming, Rinning, & Financing your own Multi-media Company (tape 1 of 1), 2-21-1996 (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Exploring New Financial Territories (tape 6 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Welcome Day 2 Panel: Collaborating Abroad (tape 7 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Tape 7A of 14 Collaborating Continued... (tape 7A of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 The Art of Pitch (tape 8 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Development (tape 9 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Multi Media (tape 10 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Working with a Sales Agent (tape 11 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Legal Issues (tape 12 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Case Study (tape 13 of 14) (Box 11)
- IFFCON '95 Focus on Japan (tape 14 of 14) (Box 11)
- Sundance Prep Talk (tape 1 of 1), 1-08-1996 (Box 11)
- IFFCON Sat. Reel 1 (tape 1 of 2), 1-13-1996 (Box 11)
- IFFCON Reel 2 (1 of 1), 1-13-1996 (Box 11)
- IFFCON Reel 3 (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 1-13-1996 (Box 11)
- IFFCON Front End Financing, 1-13-1996 (Box 11)
- Archival Footage w/ Kenn Rabin (tapes 4-6 of 6), 3-23-1997 (Box 12)
- An Afternoon with Independents & PBS (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 3-07-1998 (Box 12)
- Super - 8 For the 90's Dennis Duggan (tape 1 of 1), 3-07-1998 (Box 12)
- An Evening with Jon Jost & Henry Rosenthal (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-01-1991 (Box 12)
- Documentary Producer's Workshop: Political Docs for TV and Social Change (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-11-1991 (Box 12)
- Documentary Producer's Workshop: The Narrative Doc/Light & Saraf (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-18-1991 (Box 12)
- Documentary Producer's Workshop: Writing & Distributing Docs (tapes 1-3 of 3), 4-25-1991 (Box 12)
- Feature Fix: Domestic & Foreign Pre-Sale (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-02-1992 (Box 12)
- Mind your own Business: Grantwriting (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-01-1993 (Box 12)
- Inside the Celluloid Closet (tape 2 of 2), 5-13-1996 (Box 12)
- Turnabout: Anatomy of a Documentary with Dan Bessie (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 5-20-1996 (Box 12)
- Screenwriting Guidance Straight From the Source (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-08-1997 (Box 12)
- Sell your Film: How to be your own agent w/ Donie Nelson (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-10-1997 (Box 12)
- Mind your own Business: Legal Structures Richard Lee (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-06-1993 (Box 12)
- Mind your own Business: Fundraising Theresa Tollini & Loise Lo (tape 1 & 2 of 2), 4-08-1993 (Box 12)
- Mind your own Business: Financing Alan Jacobs (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-13-1993 (Box 12)
- Feature Fix-John Pierson (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 4-09-1992 (Box 12)
- Legal & Business Issues James Schamus (tapes 1 & 2 of 2), 5-28-1992 (Box 12)